Please try this from your high school days.
ぜひ、高校の時からやってみてください
got it.
わかりました
I know it's dangerous.
やばいの知ってるんですよね
My stomach is growling all the time.
ずっとお腹鳴ってます
Is your neck starting to hurt?
首痛くなってきた?
My neck is starting to hurt.
首痛くなってきました
Sometimes my hair is open.
髪型開けたりもあり
You look good in that uniform.
似合ってるね、制服
thank you.
ありがとうございます
As expected.
さ すがです
How have you been?
元気してましたか?
I was fine.
元気でした
How are you?
元 気でした?
Ikazu is so erotic.
いかずエロいですね
People don't say it's very erotic.
あまりエロいって言われないんですよね
Oh, really?
あ、そう?
It's very erotic though.
めちゃくちゃエロいけど
It looks a bit like a toilet.
ちょっとトイレスに見えそうだね、
here.
ここ
Are you okay?
大丈夫か?
It's been a while, I've uploaded it many times since then,
ちょっとね、あれから何回もアップしてたけど、
It wasn't easy to do.
なかなかやらなかったですね
Because it's this body.
この体だからさ
I'm already calling you a pervert, but I wore the panties you gave me about 5 times.
もう変態言っちゃうけど、 前もらったパンティで5回ぐらいや
I was there.
っちゃ いました
sorry.
すみません
please.
ぜひ
please?
ぜひ?
please.
ぜひ
I wonder what this person is wearing today.
この人もね、なんか今日は どんなの履いてるんだろうなー
That's what I was imagining when I came here.
っていう のを想像しながら来たんですけど
I wonder what kind of shoes she's wearing.
ど んなの履いてるんだろう
The line is terrible, after all.
ラインがやばいですよね、やっぱり
How many years have you been using these panties?
このパンティは何年ぐらいで使用してるんですかね?
About a year and a half.
1年半ぐらい
It's quite old.
結構古いですね
It's old.
古いですね
I'm pretty sure I got it before, and I've been saying it since high school.
前もらったのは確か、高校の時から言ってましたね
Ah, yes.
あ、 そうそう
That's already dirty.
あれはもう汚い
I've been keeping it a secret for a long time now.
もうずーっと 秘密とかに入れてますね
Please take it in.
入れとってください
is that so.
そうですか
This is a strange question, but when was the last time you had an edge?
変な質問するんですけど、 最近エッジしたのって いつですか?
Quiet.
おとつい
Are you your boyfriend?
彼氏さんですか?
no.
いや
Who are you?
誰ですかね?
Oh, is it private?
あ、プライベートですか
Has it been properly denied?
ちゃんと否認はされてるんですか?
Just in case.
一応
Please leave this alone, Mr. Nakata.
ここだけにしておいてよ、中田氏は
Mr. Nakata didn't do that, right?
中田氏はしてないんでしょ?
I haven't.
してない
There's no mention of her boyfriend, but maybe she broke up with him?
彼氏さんの話出てこないけど、 も しかして別れた?
Understood.
分かりました
After all, that's what it feels like.
やっぱり、 そんな感じがしますね
Understood.
分かりました
Did you do it before?
前しましたっけ?
I did it before.
前してた
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
That's what caused it.
それが原因できてたからね
Looking at the thumbnail, you can see that he has traveled to many places.
サムネ見てると、 いろんなところ旅行してますよね
You went to a cold place the other day, right?
この前、寒いところ行ってたでしょ?
Oh, sure.
ああ、確かに
Well, there was a scene like that in the thumbnail.
じゃあ、サムネに そういうシーンがあったんで
Um, I'm not a stalker.
あの、 ストーカーじゃないですよ
Look, I'm watching.
見て、見てるんですよ
thank you.
ありがたい
It's amazing here, that's for sure.
ここはすごいですよね、確かに
surely.
確かに
This is amazing.
これすごいんですよね
a little bit,
ちょっと、
It's going to go down that far.
そ こまで降りちゃうんだね
It rained too much, didn't it?
降りすぎたよね
A lot.
だいぶ
I know it's dangerous.
やばいの知ってるんですよね
That word is dangerous.
危険ですね、その言葉
Well then, that's the best one.
じゃあ、もう一番ですね
This is it.
これね
This is terrible.
やばいです
This is how it happened.
こうなった
I put my mouth in it.
口を入れました
Let your mouth fall out
口も抜けちゃおう
mosquito.
か
My nose is scratchy and itchy.
鼻 がちがちがして、かゆいてて
It's terrible.
最悪やばい
It was there, right?
そこにあったんじゃ、そう
I had it the other day.
この前、前ました
Are you going to laugh soon?
もうすぐ笑そうなの?
LOL I'll come over there for a second.
笑 そ っちに来るわ、ちょっと
It's okay to laugh.
笑っていいよ
Really?
ほんまに?
LOL Coco Coco card.
笑 コ ッ ココカードしてる
lol Does it tingle like this?
笑 こんなチクチクする?
lol It's okay.
笑 大丈夫
Lol lol It's a perverted ajis that smells good.
笑 匂い入れる変態アジスだな、もう
What does it smell like?
どんな匂いしますか?
It smells really good,
めちゃくちゃいい匂いしてますよ、
recently.
最近
I want to go home for a while.
ちょっと帰っておきたいです
Wasn't your stomach growling?
お腹鳴ってたんじゃない?
Now.
今の
My stomach is growling all the time.
ずっとお腹鳴ってます
LOL Is your stomach growling?
笑 お 腹 鳴ってる?
LOL Well then, let's take this one off, which I'm proud of.
笑 じゃあさ、ちょっとこれさ、自慢のこれ外しちゃおうか、
Come here for a moment.
ちょっとこっち来て
Yeah, ah, yeah.
うん、あ、うん
Can you please take it off?
あれ、脱いでもらおうかな?
That's terrible.
やばいね
It's the best.
最高だよ
Isn't it open?
開いてない?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
not at all.
全然
lol I got a little scared.
笑 ちょっと 怖くなっちゃった
lol That's weird
笑 変 わって
do not have?
ない?
picture?
え?
You don't even play sports, do you?
ス ポーツもしてないんでしょ?
Nothing now.
今何も
I haven't.
してない
I wonder how he got his body in such a good position.
どうやってこんなにいい体位置してるんだろうね
Because it's okay.
いいからです
wonderful.
素晴らしい
That's wonderful.
素晴らしいですね
Shall I come in?
入っちゃおうかな?
LOL Hey, hey.
笑 ちょい、ちょい
It's really good.
めっちゃいいです
lol Eyes, cute eyes?
笑 目、目かわいい?
Yeah, your eyes are cute.
うん、目かわいい
That's really nice.
めっちゃよろしいね
lol Did you drink too much?
笑 飲 みすぎ?
Drink tingly.
ヒリヒリ飲む
Lol lol I drink tingly.
笑 ヒリヒリ飲む
LOL Oh, is that okay?
笑 あ、いいの?
Wait, forever.
待ってくれよ、ずっと
drink
飲む
Sugi?
す ぎ?
Ah, it's delicious.
あ、おいしいわ
Isn't it good?
よくない?
Are you going there?
そっち行く?
Yeah.
うん
lol
笑
Are you crying when I touch you?
触 り泣いてない?
I just feel like I'm crying when I touch you.
触り泣いてる気がするだけだよ
That's what it is.
そういうことね
Just being touched
触られてただけで
a little bit.
ちょっと
If you check it out, you can turn around.
チ ェックしたら鼻に回っていいよ
It hurts, it hurts.
痛い、痛い
lol Does it hurt?
笑 痛い?
Enter Smile.
スマイル入って
It's still no good.
まだダメだよ
Because it feels so good.
めっちゃ気持ちいいんだから
I want you to talk.
喋っとほしいな
It's too luxurious.
贅沢いすぎるな
Inside because it was amazing.
すごいにしたから、中で
Oh, that's terrible.
あ、やばい
Are you not trying to see it?
見ようとしてない?
No.
ダメだよ
still.
まだ
I need more people.
もうちょっと人欲しいな
Big success.
大成功
Sorry.
ごめんね
Would you like that?
そっちがいいですか?
Yeah.
うん
Can you continue around here for a little while longer?
ここら辺はもうちょっと続けてくれる?
Yeah.
うん
Ah, it feels good.
あ、気持ちいい
My jaw hurts.
あごが痛い
jaw pain
あご痛
stomach?
い?
Well then, let's extinguish ourselves.
じゃあ 消気しようか
Have you ever had to wait?
イラ待ちをしたことないですか?
Ah, I'm warm.
あ、温まっちゃった
Try putting it below.
下に入れてみてね
Hold your head.
首持って
Good.
よいしょ
Is it okay?
いいから?
Yes, try it.
そう、入れてみてね
Now, it's decided.
さあ、決まって
I'm sure you can draw yourself?
きっと本人を描いていいかな?
please.
どうぞ
My legs are trembling.
足がプルプルしてるじゃん
wait a minute.
ちょっと 待って
transformation?
変態?
transformation.
変態
I might have a bad armpit today.
今日脇臭いかもしれない
really like.
大好き
Can I put them all on?
全部つけちゃっていい?
Okay.
よ いしょ
I'm back.
帰ってきた
out
出
It won't come.
て こないね
It was too close.
奥に寄すぎたな
You've been working hard lately.
頑張ってたね、最近